Good evening everyone. Tonight I want to
share three powerful lessons about
leadership and innovation.
>> Okay. So this output is not from V3. In
fact, we have a new version of the text
to video model from Alibaba which can
now natively generate audio. So this is
the second model of review 3 which has
this capability. Watch this.
>> Do you know one 2.5 preview? Yes, I come
from the model.
And I'm going to say that this is
actually a really really good model. It
synchronized the audios almost
perfectly, especially when it comes to
human characters. Here is another
example.
>> Yeah, I know some tricks.
>> Now, the good thing is that compared to
V3, it can generate up to 10 seconds
videos. Also, you can have an image to
video and it's capable of generating
videos at 1080p. Now, for speech
synchronization, you will probably see
some issues if you are animating
characters, but overall the audio
effects are very relevant to the scene.
So, watch this.
[snorts]
Go on, GET OFF MY PROPERTY. NO VISITORS
today or any day.
>> Okay. So, overall I think it's a pretty
good although there might be like some
synchronization issues but I have seen
some other examples where the synchroniz
synchronization even for non-human
characters is pretty accurate. So, for
example, watch this.
>> We use words like honor, code, loyalty.
We use these words as the backbone of a
life spent defending something. You use
them as a punchline. we use.
>> Yeah, pretty incredible stuff,
especially given that V3 was released
during IO just a few months ago and now
the one team is able to kind of
replicate the same results and same
quality and it can do very complex
scenes. So, for example, here's another
one.
As you can see, this gives you the
ability to have very complex camera
movements and especially that 10 second
duration helps a lot. Now, I have seen
some example from people generating
longer than 10-second videos. So, here
is one from D Studio project. This
specific scene is a little graphic.
>> [groaning and screaming]
[screaming]
>> Okay, you can see there is a small
glitch and that's probably coming from
stitching two videos together. The
consistency is pretty amazing and
especially like if you look here the
quality of effects is pretty incredible
as well. So if you want to test the
model you can provide a reference image
along with text prompt and then it will
animate it or you can just provide a
direct text prompt that is going to
generate a video based on that. So here
are a few other examples and then we're
going to look at some of the technical
details.
>> THE PERIMETER DO NOT RAISE THE BROKEN
UNKNOWN ENERGY ACTIVE.
>> FALL BACK. FALL BACK NOW.
>> And it's pretty incredible that you can
not only generate sounds, but those are
extremely relevant to the scene.
Especially like in this UFO scene, you
can actually see the audio effects that
changes based on the relevation of the
UFO.
[music]
>> [screaming]
>> Okay, so this one is especially kind of
crazy because you can see that it was
able to generate a scene for a video
game and then you can actually hear the
subject when the subject is firing, he
is saying die, die, right? Also, it
added the effects along with the ammo
and it actually changes which is pretty
incredible. Now this one especially is a
lot of fun and kind of shows the world
understanding of this video model
>> and that's why you NEED THE UPGRADE PACK
>> especially when it introduces the cat
and the cat sound. It seems to be at the
perfect moment. Now the model is already
available on file if you want to test it
out. They also have some examples which
will help you get started but we don't
know whether Alibaba is going to
actually open source this specific
model. They have open source the
previous versions but here is the
official release. So they are launching
one 2.5 preview and then they say that
it says to reshape the future of visual
generation with a new architecture and
powerful features. Those include native
multimodality, deep alignment and then
this adopts a new unified framework for
both understanding and generation
flexibly supporting the input and output
of text, image, video and audio. And
that's kind of what we have seen that
the model is able to not only generate
correct videos but also corresponding
sound effects as well and the text
generation also seems to be pretty
accurate. Now, apart from this specific
release, the Alibaba team has been
extremely busy. Okay. So, a few days
ago, they also released one animate
which basically gives you the ability to
animate a specific image based on a
driving video. So, for example, let's
have a look at this. This is the
original video and this is the generated
video.
>> Rick Sorcin,
>> is there a reason why I should let you
in?
>> Look, I look, I'm just trying to ditch
the cops, okay? I I don't really care if
you let me in or not.
>> Mr. Spectre will be right with you.
>> What?
>> Can I get you anything? A coffee or
bottle of water?
>> I know.
>> So, this is pretty incredible, right?
The the movements are exactly as the
driving video. And I was actually pretty
happy about that. But now we have this
new model which can also generate audio,
which is kind of crazy. Here are some
other examples from people. Uh, I'm
going to put links to all of these
videos in the video description. And you
can see that this is the original input
and the movements that are being
generated is are really incredible and
very close to the original input. Here
are a few other examples. And in some
cases, it's extremely hard to even
figure out. Technology is kind of going
in a very scary direction, especially
now people will be able to generate
these deep fakes. The one 2.2 animate
model is opensource. People have built
custom workflows. Especially there's a
comfy UI workflow that is available. You
can use it to animate your images based
on an input video. And I think
especially with this new model, it will
be able to generate even better videos.
But it's kind of crazy where the
technology is going. It's so easy to
generate these AI videos and in some
cases
it's hard to distinguish between what's
real and what's fake. That being said,
this also opens up a whole bunch of
possibilities that were not even
imaginable before. So, let me know what
you think about this release and
generative media in general. Now, to get
started, you'll need to sign up on one.
video and here you can use this new
model. I'll probably create a more
detailed video on this and hopefully
we're going to have soon information
whether this model is going to be open
weight or not. But I hope you found this
video useful. Thanks for watching and as
always see you in the next one.